National Railroad Adjustment Board, First Division, Awards Publications 6356 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Railroad Adjustment Board, First Division, Awards Publications
1937- 1951
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Railroad Adjustment Board
6356 PUBS
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
.
8054933
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 29, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5837: National Railroad Adjustment Board Case Files
8054933
- Vol. III: Awards 401-594, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Awards 401 to 594, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume III, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: National Railroad Adjustment Board
    Notes: National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, IL
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Vol. IV: Awards 595-788, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Awards 595 to 788, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume IV, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Vol. V: Awards 789-1000, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Awards 789 to 1,000, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume V, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Vol. VI: Awards 1001-1200, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Awards 1001 to 1200, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume VI, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Vol. VII: Awards 1201-1400, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Awards 1201 to 1400, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume VII, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Vol. VIII: Awards 1401-1600, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Awards 1401 to 1600, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume VIII, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Vol. IX: Awards 1601-1800, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Awarrds 1601 to 1800, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume IX, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Vol. X: Awards 1801-2000, 1936; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Awards 1801 to 2000, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume X, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Vol. XI: Awards 2001-2065, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Awards 2001 to 2065, First Division Nationla Adjustment Board Volume XI, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Vol. XII: Awards 2066-2200, 1937; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Awards 2066 to 2200, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XII, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Vol. XIII: Awards 2201-2400, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Awards 2201 to 2400, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XIII, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Vol. XIV: 2401-2600, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Awards 2401 to 2600, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XIV, 1939; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Vol. XV: Awards 2601-2800, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Awards 2601 to 2800, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XV, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Vol. XVI: Awards 2801-3000, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Awards 2801 to 3000, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XVI, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Vol. XVII: Awards 3001-3125, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Awards 3001 to 3125, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XVII, 1938; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Vol. XVIII: Awards 3126-3200, 1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Awards 3126 to 2300, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XVIII, 1938; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Vol. XIX: Awards 3201-3400, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Awards 3201 to 3400, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XIX, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Vol. XX: Awards 3401-3600, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Awards 3401 to 3600, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XX, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Notes: National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago IL
- Vol. XXI: Awards 3601-3800, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Awards 3601 to 3800, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XXI, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Vol. XXII: Awards 3801-4000, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Awards 3801 to 4000, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XXII, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Vol. 33: Awards 4300-4425, 1939; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Awards 5501 to 5650, First Division National Railroad Adjustment BoardVolume XXXII, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Vol. 34: Awards 4426-4550, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Awards 5651 to 5800, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XXXIII, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Vol. 35: Awards 4551-4675, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Awards 6101 to 6250, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XXXVII, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Vol. 36: Awards 4676-4785, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 33 4300 to 4425, 1935; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Notes: O. L. Tuley
- Vol. 37: Awards 4786-4899, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 34 4426 to 4550, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Vol. 38: Awards 4900-5000, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 35 4551 to 4673, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Vol. XXXII: Awards 5501-5650, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 36 4677 to 4785, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Vol. XXXIII: Awards 5651-5800, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 37 4786 to 4899, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Vol. XXXVII: Awards 6101-6250, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 38 4900 to 5000, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Vol. XXXVIII: Awards 6251-6350, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Awards 6251 to 6350, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XXXVIII, 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Vol. XXXIX: Awards 6351-6500, 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Awards 6351 to 6500, First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume XXXIX, 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: National Railroad Adjustment Board Chiacgo, IL
- Vol. 65: Awards 7590-7708, 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL. Volume 60 Awards 9241 to 9415, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Vol. 66: Awards 7709-7764, 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL. Volume 62 Awards 9571 to 9720, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Vol. 60: Awards 9241-9415, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL. Volume 63 Awards 9721 to 9870, 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Vol. 62: 9571-9720, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: First Division Vol. 63 7421 to 7496, 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Vol. 63: Awards 9721-9870, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: First Division Vol. 65 7590 to 7708, 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Vol. 63: Awards 9721-9870, 1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  Copy 2.
  - Item 1: First Division Col. 66 7709 to 7764, 1943; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Vol. 70: Awards 10621-10770, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL. Volume 70 Awards 10621 to 10770, 1945; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Vol. 76: Awards 11501-11625, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago IL Volume 76 Awards 11501 to 11625, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Vol. 76: Awards 11501-11625, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL. Volume 76 Awards 11501 to 11625, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Notes: Second copy
- Vol. 77: Awards 11626-11775, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL. Volume 77 Awards 11626 to 11775, 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Notes: Interpretation of Award 11158 (Docket No. 19727)
- Vol. 82: Awards 12355-12504, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL Volume 82 Awards 12355 to 12504, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Notes: Interpretation of Award 11883 (Docet No. 22066)
- Vol. 85: Awards 12718-12842, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Chicago, ILL Volume 85 Awards 12718 to 12842, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Vol. 85: Awards 12718-12842, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: First Division National Railroad Adjustment Board Volume 85 Awards 12718 to 12842, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Notes: copy 2
- Vol. 118: Awards 13790-13944, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 118 12790 -12944, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes: J.N. Marcoux
- Vol. 120: Awards 14056-14175, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 120 14056-14175, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Notes: J. N. Marcoux
- Vol. 123: Awards 14485-14619, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: National Railroad Adjustment Board First Division Vol. 123 14485-14619, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)